<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Rim-Effect Reborn: Asari and Reapers</name>
	<author>Vanilla Expanded Team and Co.</author>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.5</li>
    </supportedVersions>
	<packageId>RimEffectReborn.AsariReapers</packageId>
	<modIconPath IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">RimEffect/ModIcon</modIconPath>
	<modDependencies>
        <li>
			<packageId>RimEffectReborn.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Rim-Effect Reborn: Core</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2479560240</steamWorkshopUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>RimEffectReborn.Core</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<description>Rim Effect is a large overhaul mod series, adding the story, races, objects, and conflicts of Mass Effect universe into RimWorld. The Mass Effect elements are not meant to stand out, and as such are blended into the RimWorld style by utilising the same naming conventions and writing styles.

Much like Vanilla Factions Expanded, the Rim Effect mod series comes divided into sub-modules, firstly to allow the players to pick exactly what elements they want in their games, secondly to ease the production and design process.

Rim Effect Asari is a first big race module in Rim Effect mod series, adding the story, races, objects and conflicts of Mass Effect Universe into RimWorld. This module introduces the Asari Republics, a true democracy culture known for finding the Citadel and leading the Citadel Council.

As an antagonist, alongside the Asari Republics come the Reapers, a race of sentient machines bound to continue the cycle and eradicate all life in the universe as we know it. The Reapers are an end-game threat that works similarly to VFE Mechanoids. Their ships land all around the planet, allowing them to amass a bigger force with every ship that makes planetfall.

This module includes all the iconic weapons and apparel of the Asari, a new playable race, Reaperised enemies and Reaper ships sporting a vast amount of new weapons, a new starting scenario and much, much more.

CC BY-NC-ND 4.0</description>
</ModMetaData>